Okay.
Man.
Oh no!
Wait!
MAKING A SAFE WORKING ENVIRONMENT
Whitetip.
Tawny nurse, Flapnose ray, Sandbar,
Sand tiger,
Bluestripe snapper.
Manta!
Geu-ru, you're here.
The smallest whitetip's tail is torn.
It's because the biggest sandbar
keeps attacking it.
Seven of the bluestrip snappers are gone
compared to the last week.
The tawny nurse ate one today again.
And Yellow is hurt.
Its left fin is torn,
so it keeps swimming to the right.
It needs to be treated right away.
I'll check if you say so
because you've never been wrong.
Give me a second.
Geu-ru, do you know
you were on fire again?
The aquarists were amazed
at how you noticed those things
when they couldn't at all.
I wonder how and what you can see.
I wish I could explain it to them.
I've been your friend over ten years,
but it still surprises me too.
So I can't imagine how others feel, right?
What I mean is since you're my bestie,
I've become super popular
at the aquarium as well.
Thank you, Geu-ru!
-Bye, Geu-ru.
-Farewell, Na-mu.
I'm home.
-You're home.
-Oh, you're back.
CHICKEN BOWL
Hi, Geu-ru.
MOVE TO HEAVEN
4, HANEULSAN-RO 29-GIL
I'm home.
Come on in.
Let's eat.
CHOCOLATE MILK, YOGURT, DRINKING YOGURT
Okay.
All righty.
No.
Look.
I prefer broken yolk.
Thank you for the food.
How is your egg? Is it good?
I always like an egg you fry, Dad.
Geu-ru, do you want me
to show you how to fry an egg?
But that's what you're good at.
And I'm good at doing the dishes.
You said each one should do
what they are good at.
Wouldn't it be nice if you can do it
when I'm not around?
Why wouldn't you be around?
Are you going somewhere?
It's because I also want
to have an egg you fry at times.
Then I'll learn it right away.
First, open the gas valve
before using the stove.
Then, take out an egg from the fridge.
Hello? This is Move to Heaven.
Sure, I understand.
We'll be there shortly.
Is it a job?
Yes.
Let's see if we are all ready.
Good. Shall we get going?
He got hurt last week
at the factory he worked at
but suffered alone all weekend
without seeing a doctor.
The doctor who came with the police said
because his severe wound
was left untreated,
it caused tetanus or sepsis.
Something of that sort.
What about his family?
His colleague came instead of his parents
and asked me to take care of things.
But take care of what and how?
My boss wants
everything gone and cleaned out.
Gosh.
Since you are an expert at this,
you'll take care of everything, right?
That's correct.
Then we'll get on it
after we check the scene.
Please finish it as soon as possible.
Mr. Kim Seon-u,
you passed away on April 11th, 2020.
We're from Move to Heaven.
I'm Han Jeong-u.
I'm Han Geu-ru.
We'll now begin to help you
with your final move.
MOVE TO HEAVEN
JIN RAMEN
CU CONVENIENCE STORE
20% OFF SALE
Dad.
Are you thinking of the deceased again?
Yes.
What kind of person was Mr. Kim Seon-u?
STAFF: KIM SEON-U
He was a young intern at the factory
who started working
right after high school
and just started
to study to go to college.
His dream was…
GO FOR A PERMANENT JOB!
…to be a permanent employee.
What do you think?
Mr. Kim liked instant cup noodles.
Especially, Jin Ramen, the spicy flavor.
He usually had triangular gimbap
from a convenience store.
He liked all kinds of flavors of gimbap
like pollack roe mayo,
tuna mayo, and Kimchi anchovy.
And he seemed to be sensitive to smells.
He had fabric refreshers
in both his bag and room.
Am I wrong?
No, you are not wrong.
I think he had the cup noodles
not because he liked them,
but because he had no time
to eat properly while working.
And as for gimbap for dinner,
he didn't care for flavors,
but he picked any kind that was on sale.
He had a pair of underwear, nail clippers,
and a fabric refresher in his bag.
It means he was bothered
by the smell of his sweat and dirty nails.
So I assume he was a very neat young man.
There is one more thing.
Mr. Kim Seon-u loved
his parents very much.
You've found
the most important thing, Geu-ru.
UNDERSTANDING OF CYBER COURSES
THE LATE KIM SEON-U, REST IN PEACE
-Are you all done?
-Yes, for now.
The deodorization will be done in 24 hours
since the room is small.
I'm glad you're finished
quicker than I expected.
Do you have the contact information
for Mr. Kim's parents?
We have the number for his work only.
His funeral is held at Sunae Hospital,
so they're probably there.
I see. Thank you.
YEONGSIN DORMITORY
It's a tiny room,
but it was still his home.
Yet, he has so little to throw away.
That's right.
It's grim to see people
who had too much stuff,
but it's also sad to look at
how little someone could leave behind.
I agree.
Well, you guys are all done, right?
We're stopping by his funeral
before we go home.
You found things that bother you,
didn't you?
I feel bad
since he was so young to die.
Although it's cleaning up stuff
left by the deceased,
it's the same
as cleaning up a moving house.
But you care about
the deceased like no one does.
That's why your work is
always my first priority over others.
I'm always grateful.
Okay, I'd better be going.
Sure, thank you.
Wait.
Look.
CU CONVENIENCE STORE
That's where Mr. Kim
bought gimbap every day.
19:50, January 3rd. Anchovy gimbap,
buy-one-get-one-free. 1,000 won.
19:26, January 6th. Tuna gimbap,
19:16 January 10th. Pollack roe,
buy-one-get-one-free. 1,000 won.
We should go see Mr. Kim's parents now.
Right, we should.
JOSEON TECH INCORPORATED
LIM YEONG-GEUN
Seon-u's parents,
you need to listen carefully.
Ma'am, this is
not a workplace accident.
No workplace accident.
WORKPLACE ACCIDENT
A workplace accident is
being injured at work.
But for Seon-u's case, he was at his dorm.
I mean he died while sleeping in his room.
And he even skipped work without notice.
UNAUTHORIZED ABSENCE
So the company holds no liability.
LIABILITY
Nevertheless, we want
to take moral responsibility.
You know what that means, right?
This is a token of our condolences.
Understood?
Man, we feel really bad
about what happened.
Everyone loved Seon-u.
What a tragedy.
So, ma'am and sir, don't lose heart. Okay?
Hang in there.
Let's go.
I'm sorry for your loss.
We cleaned and collected
what Mr. Kim Seon-u left at his dorm.
We're here to give something to you.
His belongings!
They brought what Seon-u had
from his room.
Thank you.
JOSEON TECH, 5 PERSONS
Machine 13 is down.
It needs to be fixed by tonight.
Who will do it? Newbie?
Do I work alone?
Everyone is busy with their situation.
Don't be fussy. You can do it.
Yes, sir. I'll get right on it.
Sir, can I take sick leave tomorrow?
Sick leave? Suddenly? What's wrong?
I hurt my leg while working.
Then go see a doctor now.
You must come to work no matter what.
Clinics nearby are all closed.
Let me see a doctor in the morning.
Don't say a thing
like you got hurt while working.
You can get sacked
for mentioning a workplace accident.
I understand.
I will be at work on time.
-Reporters better stay quiet.
-Yes, sir.
What is this mess?
Why do I have to be here anyway?
I mean, it's heartbreaking.
Good grief. It could've been worse.
It's good
that Seon-u's parents are hillbillies
and can't do this.
If they could,
they would've blown this up
and gotten many of us sacked.
Let's go if you're done.
Parents are bound to wail
over their child's death,
so a quiet funeral like this is very rare.
We should be grateful
that they're like this, okay?
Have a drink.
What's wrong?
Well, Geu-ru.
Wait outside, will you?
Sure.
Say that again.
You're grateful that they can't speak?
Damn, who the heck is he?
What?
Hey, what are you doing?
-What the-- Hey!
-Sir!
-If you want to talk, let go of me!
Ma'am.
These people are
the ones Seon-u worked with.
If you have anything you want to say,
say it now. It's okay.
"I told Seon-u
when the economy is as bad as today,
he should be thankful
for the job and the paycheck.
That he should work hard."
"He couldn't go to college
like his friends
because we didn't have money,
but since you gave him the job,
I told him to give his best at work."
So answer me.
Did my son ever slack off
or do his job half-heartedly?
Did he ever say no to your orders
and try to back out from doing his job?
Would you have done this
if he were one of your own?
Mom.
WAKE UP AT 6 A.M.!
MUST ENTER THE OPEN UNIVERSITY!
MUST GET SCHOLARSHIP
WHEN ENTERING THE UNIVERSITY
Take this back.
I wouldn't take a penny for my son's life
even if I had to die without it.
I'll be back when the IV infusion is done.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
Why are you following me?
Well, actually--
If you come closer,
I'll call security.
There's something I want.
From me?
Yes.
I really want to have it.
What do you want?
Oh no.
What are you looking at?
That thing.
I want to have that.
Rajidae, Rajiformes,
Chondrichthyes, Chordata, Animalia.
-We're in the lounge.
-Its mouth protrudes.
Its length is three times
of space between eyes.
On the back of the body disc,
on the midline, around the eyes--
Geu-ru!
-Uh? Dad!
-Are you okay?
It's okay. Dad is here.
I'm sorry he startled you.
It's okay.
I wasn't going to take it from her.
I just wanted to ask where she got it.
But she said it's not purchasable.
Do you want it that badly?
Yes.
Why do you want it so much?
I want to give it
to Mr. Kim Seon-u as a gift.
Son!
I know you hate this,
but let me hug you just once.
-No way!
-Don't be like that. Just this once.
You said we shouldn't force things
on someone we love.
Why did I say all those right things?
But let me hug you this once.
Don't be so cheap.
I don't like a hug,
but I won't make you pay.
I'm not cheap.
I want chocolate milk.
That's the definition of being cheap.
We have to go
to give Mr. Kim Seon-u a gift.
-Come on, just a little longer.
-Dad.
Please stop now.
BANKBOOK, KIM SEON-U
Mom and Dad, I'm making money now.
Every day, I'm grateful I'm able to work.
I'll pay for your knee surgery, Mom.
I'll take care of Dad's cataract.
PRECIOUS CHILD
I'm studying for college entrance.
You can live in comfort
once I got a permanent job.
I'm in the neighborhood. I will stop by.
I'd feel better
when things are sorted out.
Okay.
Geu-ru.
I need to go see Mr. Oh, the lawyer.
Come with me.
I'll stay here and watch the fish.
See you later.
-Then I'll make it quick.
-Okay.
Son!
LAWYER OH HYUN-CHANG
The light turned green.
Hey.
-Hey, kid.
-Yes?
DAD
Dad?
Where are you? Why aren't you back, Dad?
Why aren't you saying anything?
-My Geu-ru--
-Dad!
I'm…
sorry.
Dad!
Dad?
Your call cannot be connected.
Please leave a message--
Honeycomb stingray.
Myliobatidae, Rajiformes,
Chondrichthyes, Chordata, Animalia.
The margin is nearly straight.
The space between small eyes is flat.
Its tail is long.
-One, two, three.
-All right. Okay.
A sharp barb on the front that extends--
DRIVER'S LICENSE, HAN GEU-RU
Fasten the seat belt.
Start the car while stepping on the brake.
Shift the gear to D.
The accelerator is like a water balloon.
Gently step on it
in order not to burst it.
Now go search for my dad.
Aren't we there yet?
He's in critical condition!
Learn how to drive, asshole!
Is this a joke? The road is not all yours!
DAD
I'm not involved in an accident.
I'm not hurt.
Geu-ru.
My dad always comes to pick me up.
But I didn't listen to him today.
He told me not to drive by myself,
but I broke the promise.
That's why he didn't come to pick me up.
It's not like that, Geu-ru.
That's not what happened.
CREMATION
Geu-ru.
Geu-ru, you shouldn't do that.
Dad is coming home.
Geu-ru, you aren't supposed to that.
-Dad is coming home with me.
-Geu-ru.
Let him do as he wishes.
Geu-ru, you can take your time
to scatter his ashes.
Be with your dad as long as you want.
Geu-ru!
Son!
Dad
is
always
with you, Geu-ru.
You know that, right?
THE LATE HAN JEONG-U
Dad is always with Geu-ru.
Who are you?
Who's asking?
Well, I am…
Wait, you're a stranger.
You can't barge in here.
A stranger?
I'm not a stranger.
Geu-ru, someone is here. Come out quickly.
No beer?
Han Geu-ru!
Hey, who gives you the right to do this?
I do.
Sorry?
Because as of today,
this house belongs to me.
Subtitle translation by: Jean S Kim